var a={
allquestions:[
{
    question:"what is html?",
    id:"id1",
    answer:"hyper text markup language",
    Options:["hyper text markup language","hype text markup language","hypo text markup language","hyper text makeup language"],

},
{
question:"what is css",
id:"id2",
answer:"cascading style sheets",
options:["cascading sauce sheets","cascading style sheets","cascading style shots","casatta style sheets"],

},
{
question:"what is cpp",
id:"id3",
answer:"c plus plus",
options:["c pora po","c po po","c pour pour","c plus plus"],
},
{
    question:"what is js",
    id:"id4",
    answer:"java script",
    options:["jhonty shades","joker shadows","java script","none of the above"],
},
{
    question:"who invented js",
    id:"id5",
    answer:"brendian eich",
    options:["brendian eich","ross taylor","williamson","boult"],
},
{
    question:"2+3",
    id:"id6",
    answer:5,
    options:[1,2,3,5],
},
{
question:"The  object can be written without the window prefix.",
id:"id7",
answer:"window.screen",
options:["window screen","ross taylor","williamson","boult"],
},
{question:"The HTML element is used to show a video on a web page.",
id:"id8",
answer:" video",
options:["video","cascading style sheets","cascading style shots","casatta style sheets"],
},
{
question:"ascii mean",
id:"id9",
answer:"american standard code of information interchange",
options:["american standard code of information interchange","hype text markup language","hypo text markup language","hyper text makeup language"],
},
{question:" ascii value of a",
id:"id10",
answer:95,
options:[96,98,95,100],
},
{
question:"full form of DOM",
id:"id11",
answer:"document object model",
options:["data object model","data orient model","date object model","data object mode"],
},
{question:"css founder",
id:"id12",
answer:"hakon wiam lee",
options:["haon wiam lee","ross taylor","williamson","boult"],
},
{
    question:"founder of c",
    id:"id13",
    answer:"dennis ritchie",
    options:["jhonty shades","joker shadows","dennis ritchie","none of the above"],
},
{question:"what is constructor",
id:"id14",
answer:"special keyword",
options:["unspecial keyword","aspecial keyword","date object model","data object model"],
},
{
question:"ceo of google",
id:"id15",
answer:"sundar pichaiah",
options:["mark zuckerberg","sundar pichaiah","satyanadela","sundar"],
},
{
question:"ceo of facebook",
id:"id16",
answer:"mark zuckerberg",
options:["mark zuckerberg","sundar pichaiah","satyanadela","sundar"],
},
{
question:"ship of desert",
id:"id17",
answer:"camel",
options:["ross taylor","williamson","boult","camel"],
},
{
question:"ceo of apple",
id:"id18",
answer:"steve jobs",
options:["sundar pichaiah","satyanadela","sundar","steve jobs"],
},
{
  question:"how many seconds makes an hour" ,
  id:"id19",
  answer:60,
  options:[45,63,96,60],
},
{
question:"how many days in a week",
id:"id20",
answer:7,
options:[7,5,6,1],
},
]

}